{
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7oise_Rosay",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jacques_Feyder",
    "human_readable": "Fran\u00e7oise Rosay is married to Jacques Feyder.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886497259140015,
            "question": "Is Jacques Feyder married to Fran\u00e7oise Rosay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9214822053909302,
            "question": "Who is Fran\u00e7oise Rosay married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630246877670288,
            "question": "What is the name of Fran\u00e7oise Rosay's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6478326916694641,
            "question": "Who are some notable people who were in a relationship with Fran\u00e7oise Rosay?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6068633198738098,
            "question": "Were Fran\u00e7oise Rosay and Jacques Feyder both actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5104107856750488,
            "question": "What is the profession of Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48001039028167725,
            "question": "Did Fran\u00e7oise Rosay and Jacques Feyder collaborate on any projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3993934690952301,
            "question": "Who are some famous actresses who worked with Jacques Feyder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3739575147628784,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jacques Feyder's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18125446140766144,
            "question": "What films were directed by Jacques Feyder?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fran\u00e7oise Rosay is married to Jacques Feyder.",
            "html": "yago_8745_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Jacques Feyder's career?",
            "html": "yago_8745_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous actresses who worked with Jacques Feyder?",
            "html": "yago_8745_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Fran\u00e7oise Rosay and Jacques Feyder collaborate on any projects?",
            "html": "yago_8745_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8745_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Fran\u00e7oise Rosay is married to Jacques Feyder\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there are multiple documents that mention Fran\u00e7oise Rosay being married to Jacques Feyder, as shown in the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Fran\u00e7oise Rosay was married to Jacques Feyder, thus supporting the statement that Fran\u00e7oise Rosay is married to Jacques Feyder."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}